RAHULIA KRISTANTI

(+62) 8953-2241-7891 | rahuliakristanti08@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/rahulia-kristanti | Portfolio Semarang, Central Java, 50254

SUMMARY

A associate degree of Telecommunication Technology from Universitas Telkom. Experienced as a practium assistant as well as familiar with instalation software, hardware, and troubleshooting. Currently attending a bootcamp for deepering skills in software engineering. A hardworking person who is open to full time work opportunities to develop a career in IT field and web development.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Lab Cellcom Universitas Telkom – Bandung, Indonesia

Practicum Assistant (September 2023 – November 2023)

 Assisting 60 Telecommunication Technology students to do their practicum task at Mobile Communication System course using Atoll and G-NetTrack

PT. Dirgantara Indonesia – Bandung, Indonesia

Aircraft Electrician at Divisi Electrical Sub Assembly (March 2023 – June 2023)

- Handled the varnishing process of 2 critical components that had been assembled
- Performed continuity tests on the AFCS system using NI PXIe-1065, LabVIEW, and TestStand to ensure that the components were functioning properly

Lab RLK (Electrical Circuit) Universitas Telkom – Bandung, Indonesia

Practicum Assistant (July 2021 - December 2022)

 Assisting 100 Telecommunication Technology students to do their practicum task at Electrical Circuit course using hardware such as a multimeter to calculate the magnitude of electric current, voltage, and resistance, as well as several software programs such as Multisim and Proteus

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCES

Formasi (Forum Mahasiswa Penerima Beasiswa KIP-K) – Bandung, Indonesia

Coordinator of PSDM Division (April 2022 – March 2023)

- Lead 6 members to plan and do some work program such as Upgrading and Formasi Responsi
- Success to perform webinar with national level speaker like Vina Muliana with 1000 participants

Himpunan Mahasiswa D3 Teknologi Telekomunikasi – Bandung, Indonesia

Staff of Ristek Department (March 2021 – December 2021)

Success to perform webinar with alumni of Telecommunication Technology with 100 participants

EDUCATION

Universitas Telkom – Bandung, Indonesia

D-3 Telecommunication Technology - GPA 3.93 / 4.00 (August 2020 - October 2023)

• Relevant Subjects: Programming Workshop I; Programming Workshop II

COURSES, TRAINING AND CERTIFICATIONS

Revou – Jakarta, Indonesia

Mini Course in Software Engineering (January 2023 – February 2023)

 Mini Coding Project: Landing page using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

Harisenin.com – Jakarta, Indonesia

Bootcamp in Full Stack Web Developer (January 2023)

 <u>Basic Mission Project</u>: MVP landing page using HTML and CSS.

SKILLS & ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Hard skills: Assisting, trouleshooting, software, hardware, Ms Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint), HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Soft skills: Communication, analytical thinking, problem solving, curiosity
- Language: Bahasa (Native), English (Beginner; EprT Score: 480)